This is a warning. Everything just
changed with this chart right here and
this could impact [music] the next 10
years for Bitcoin. This could be a
seismic shift. Take a look at this chart
right here. This trend line has been
broken for the first time in over 13
years. We will look back on this candle
that just broke this trend line years
[music] and years and years from now and
we will realize this was the start of it
all. Everything is about to change for
Bitcoin and I'm going to tell you what I
think happens next and what should you
do with this information. Let's get into
it. Recently, many of you have been
randomly unsubscribed from my channel
and missing just one video in a market
like this can cost you big time. So,
stop what you're doing, look down, and
make sure you are subscribed. So, here
we are. Bitcoin US dollar index and
today we are on the sixth month chart,
meaning each candle represents six
months of price action. What you notice
is that we have this yellow line drawn
on our chart. What you'll notice is that
it starts its journey back in January of
2011 when we acted as resistance. In
other words, Bitcoin was very new,
Bitcoin rose up very significantly, very
quickly, and was met with resistance at
exactly the start of this trend line. It
followed it up for the next six months
also seeing resistance from this exact
trend line and finally breaking through
in 2013 only to hold it as support later
in 2013 and create its big strong candle
to the upside. Now, I want to lay a huge
clue on you. You see how far this candle
is above this yellow line? Yes, we went
that far above not just for this
all-time high in 2013. We went about the
same percentage high back here in 2017.
In other words, when you take a measured
move from this trend line up to the top
of the candle, you can see a percentage
gain. When you do the same thing from
here up until here, it's around the same
percentage gain. Another way to do it is
to go from the top of this candle down
to this level right here, roughly in the
90s, and we were in the 90s for both. In
other words, for the top of the market
in 2013 and the top of the market in
2017, we fell all the way down to this
trend line here, but both of those
candles were roughly 90-ish percent from
our trend line. So, it's a very healthy
market. We rallied up in 2013. We came
back down, and we held support with
these two candles from Jan 2015 and July
2015. And look at those wicks protecting
this area that, years ago, was our
resistance back in 2011. So, right there
are the two most important candles to
start this trend line back in 2015,
confirming support at what used to be
our resistance. And from there, it was
one of the most prolific bull runs we
had ever had. This was the definition of
a classic bull run, and it happened with
these two historic candles here. So, we
rallied all the way up, only to be
90-ish something percent above this
trend line, and only to crash back down
holding some support. We had a huge wick
here back in 2020. Bouncing off of here
with a large wick is another important
candle because that sent us even further
up, but only was roughly 90-ish% once
again from this trend line. So, each of
the three market cycle tops for 12 years
in a row were roughly 90-ish%
from this trend line, from the top of
the candle
down to the trend line, roughly 90-ish%.
And everything changed in this recent
cycle. And this is why this is the
beginning of something monumental. This
is the beginning of something
catastrophic that's going to happen to
Bitcoin. I believe we're going to look
back at this candle years from now and
realize this was
absolutely
critical and widely overlooked. Now, I
don't know if anybody else is going to
be talking about this, but everything
just changed for Bitcoin. What do I mean
by that? Well, this time when we had our
all-time high, we were not 90-ish
something from that top of the candle to
the bottom. I mean, we were only half of
that, okay? In other words, we didn't
rally as high and this is the start.
This cycle that we just completed is the
telltale sign that something big is
going to happen next cycle and
potentially the cycle after that. It
could be devastating. It could be major.
If you're watching this video in 2027 or
2028 or 2030 or 2035, you're going to
come back and we're going to look at
this candle and we're going to talk
about how significant it was because I
believe everything just changed. We just
broke this trend line for the first time
in 13 years. In 13 years. That's almost
the entire history of Bitcoin. We've
been holding this trend line as support.
And it's not like we haven't touched
this trend line. We've touched it a lot.
We've touched it at the bottom of the
market in 2015 to confirm our support.
We touched it in the COVID crash of
2020. We touched it at the bottom of the
market in 2022 when everyone said,
"Don't buy Bitcoin at 15, 16, 17,000."
We even touched it in the beginning of
the bull run in 2023. We even came down
as support back in July of 2025. And
this candle that just printed, this
candle is hot off the press, this is the
candle that could change everything
because we quite literally closed as
resistance. Now, what's going to happen
next? Anytime you have
trend line that's broken, one thing
becomes true right away, and that's not
up for debate. This is now our
resistance, okay? Plain and simple, this
is now our resistance. Now, what I want
you to look at is what this looks like
in our next market cycle top. You look
at sort of, you know, this end of 2029,
the beginning of 2030. What price are we
at
during that period? In other words,
where what price is the trend line at
during those periods? We're talking
about over half a million-dollar
Bitcoin. I already told you that's
highly unlikely based on math. And if
you don't like math, and you just like
to guess what the new all-time high will
be, you be my guest. But those people
who like facts and math, you're
subscribed to this channel, and you
realize we may never get above this
trend line ever again. This trend line
that we were playing with for 13 years
as support and a couple years as
resistance, it's been in Bitcoin's story
since 2011. It We have 15 years of data
with this trend line. This trend line
has been our best friend for all 15
years. We might never touch this trend
line again. Why? Because our next market
cycle top is highly and likely to be up
to this trend line, and we just broke
it. We're going to start a new phase for
Bitcoin, and I believe that phase has
just begun. Now, you see, every single
cycle is getting weaker and weaker,
meaning the rise in price from the
bottom of our bear market to the top of
the next market. That percentage gain
every single cycle is getting weaker and
weaker and weaker. And don't just take
my word for it, trust math, trust
numbers. Just take the percentage gain
from the bottom to the top and then go
to the next cycle and it's a fraction of
it. And then go to the next cycle and
it's a a fraction again. And go to the
next cycle. Oh my god, it's a fraction
again. What is going on? Well, Bitcoin
is new and Bitcoin's a new asset class
that is going to go through its first
real hiccup. The market is going to
readjust, the market is going to
reassess, the market is going to reset,
we're going to build healthy market
structure and then that whole 15-year
cycle will likely repeat after that
devastation period is over. And the
devastation period may last multiple
cycles. And I believe we just saw the
first domino to fall in that next
multi-cycle
bloodbath. Trade like a tourist or go
with the pros. The SFA is where the real
ones go.
Link in description.